{"data":[{"question":"He doesn't buy a ticket every day so he has a season ticket.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"doesn't","b":"a","c":"so","d":"season","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Doesn't buy-> does buy\/buy","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Schools in England are not the same from in our country.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"Schools","b":"are not","c":"from","d":"our","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- From-> form","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"In England school children do not go to school on Saturdays with Sundays.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"children","b":"school","c":"on","d":"with","answer":"4","explain":"\n\n- With-> and","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"In some places, winter begins in November and ending in March or April.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"begins","c":"ending","d":"or","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Ending-> ends","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"You can see a lot of childs running and jumping in the snow or playing with snowballs.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"see","b":"childs","c":"in","d":"playing","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Childs-> children","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"One day their mother took them in their aunt's house to play while she went to the big city to buy some new clothes.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"took","b":"in","c":"while","d":"some","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- In-> to","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"Two old gentlemen lived in a quite street in Paris.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"gentlemen","b":"in","c":"quite","d":"Paris","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Quite-> Quiet","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"They went often for walks together in the streets when the weather was fine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"often","b":"together","c":"when","d":"was","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Went often-> often went","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"In England nobody under the age of eighteen are allowed to drink in a public bar.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"In","b":"nobody","c":"are","d":"to drink","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Are-> is","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"},{"question":"There is a prison in iceland which allows its prisoners going out without any guards to work everyday.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"is","b":"allows","c":"going","d":"to work","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- Going-> to go","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"14","type":"1"}]}